Guide to the Liberty Hyde Bailey papers, 1845-2004
Bailey, Liberty Hyde papers, 1845-2004
- Series IX. Photographs, Negatives, and Albums
  - Cornell
    - Albert Hazen Wright, Pre-Cornell, Studies in History No. 29 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Albert Hazen Wright, Pre-Cornell, Studies in History, No. 30 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Postcards: Brazil; California: redwoods, Stanford University; Germany; Grenada, B. W. I.; Haiti; Missouri; Bottom, Saba; Flying Dutchman (airplane); two unidentified (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Photographs: mostly unidentified (Box 65, Folder 8-9)
    - typescript lists: Flore de Madagaskar, Palm papers (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - 3 University forms (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Negatives
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Minnesota trip, Indians of Northern Minnesota 1886 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: "Granpa at Home" (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: "Liberty Hyde Bailey, S. Sailor Sr., H.P.S., S.M.B., E.Z.B, Nettie Etc." (Box 39, Folder 37-45)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: "Me in China and U.S. - Annette Page" (Box 39, Folder 16-21)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Annette Bailey passport photograph negatives (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Bailey Family (Box 40, Folder 2-3)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Bailey Family photographs c. 1920 (Box 39, Folder 1-15,22)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Bailey Family photographs (Box 39, Folder 25-27)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Bailey Family photographs (Box 39, Folder 30,32,35)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Bailey Family photographs (Box 39, Folder 46-54)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Bailey Homestead (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Bailiwick c. 1895 (Box 39, Folder 55)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Bailiwick (Box 39, Folder 56-65)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Bailiwick (Box 39, Folder 66)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Bailiwick c. 1895 (Box 40, Folder 1,16-23)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Bailiwick Orchards (Box 40, Folder 6-14)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Ethel Zoe and Sara M. Bailey (Box 39, Folder 23-24)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Ethel Zoe Bailey passport negative (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Liberty Hyde Bailey 1929 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Man with Horse (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Palms (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Print of Bailey family at Bailiwick (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Glass Plate Negatives: Tomato Plant (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Nitrate Negatives: Miscellaneous Negatives from Collecting trips (Box 42)
  - Miscellaneous
    - E.W. Ball, 1895 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Books by Liberty Hyde Bailey (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: A (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: B (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: C (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: D (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: E (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: F (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: G (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: H (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: L (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: M (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: O - P (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: R (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: S (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: T (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: V (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: W (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: Groups (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of People: Botanical Centers (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of Liberty Hyde Bailey (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 16, Folder 47)
- Series X. Cyanotype Photograph Albums and Negatives, 1888 - 1910
  - Photograph albums
    - 3 x 4, Print Numbers: 3.1 - 3.232, 1890 - 1897 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: No. 1 - 88, 1889 - 1891 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 89 - 184, 1889 - 1891 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 185 - 280, 1889 - 1890 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 281 - 376, 1889 - 1890 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 377 - 472, 1889 - 1891 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 473 - 496, 505 - 552, 561 - 568, 1891 - 1892 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 569 - 608, 617 - 665, 1891 - 1892 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 666 - 761, 1890 - 1891 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 762 - 857, 1889 - 1891 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 858 - 929, 938 - 953, 1889 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 954 - 1149, 1892 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 1150 - 1197, 1206 - 1237, 1892 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 1246 - 1317, 1326 - 1341, 1890 - 1893 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 1342 - 1441, 1889 - 1893 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 1442 - 1537, 1893 - 1894 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 1538 - 1633, 1894 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 1634 - 1729, 1893 - 1894 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 1730 - 1825, 1894 - 1895 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 1826 - 1833, 1842 - 1905, 1914 - 1921, 1895 - 1896 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 1922 - 1969, 1978 - 2017, 1896 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 2018 - 2114, 1895 - 1897 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 2115 - 2218, 1894 - 1896 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 2219 - 2314, 1899 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 2315 - 2322, 2339 - 2386, 2395 - 2402 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 2411 - 2458 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 2459 - 2482, 2491 - 2506 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 2507 - 2554 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 2555 - 2602 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 2603 - 2634, 2643 - 2650 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 2651 - 2698, 1903 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 2699 - 2745, 1903 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - 4 x 5, Print Numbers: 2746 - 2753, 2762 - 2765 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1 - 8, 13 - 24, 1890 - 1891 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 25 - 48, 1890 - 1891 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 49 - 72, 1890 - 1891 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 73 - 96, 1890 - 1891 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 97 - 120, 1891 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 121 - 144, 1891 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 145 - 168, 1891 (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 169 - 192, 1891 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 193 - 216, 1891 - 1892 (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 217 - 240, 1892 (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 241 - 248, 253 - 264, 1892 (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 265 - 268, 273 - 288, 1892 (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 289 - 312, 1892 - 1893 (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 313 - 338, 1892 - 1893 (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 339 - 362, 1892 - 1893 (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 363 - 386, 1892 - 1893 (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 387 - 410, 1893 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 411 - 434, 1893 (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 435 - 458, 1893 (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 459 - 482, 1893 - 1894 (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 483 - 506, 1892 - 1894 (Box 35, Folder 54)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 507 - 530, 1893 - 1894 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 531 - 554, 1893 - 1894 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 555 - 578, 1894 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 579 - 602, 1894 - 1895 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 603 - 606, 611 - 622, 1894 -1895 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 627 - 650, 1895 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 651 - 676, 1895 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 677 - 700, 1895 - 1896 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 701 - 724, 1895 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 725 - 748, 1895 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 749 - 772 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 773 - 796, 1895 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 797 - 820, 1894 - 1896 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 821 - 844, 1894 - 1896 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 845 - 868, 1896 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 869 - 892, 1896 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 893 - 916, c. 1894 - 1896 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 917 - 940, c. 1894 - 1896 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 941 - 964, c. 1894 - 1896 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 965 - 988, 1896 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 989 - 992, 997 - 1012, 1896 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1013 - 1036, 1896 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1037 - 1060, 1894 - 1896 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1061 - 1082.5, 1896 - 1897 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1083 - 1106, 1896 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1107 - 1130, 1896 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1131 - 1154, 1896 - 1897 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1155 - 1177, 1896 - 1897 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1178 - 1201 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1202 - 1227, 1897 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1228 - 1250, 1897 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1251 - 1274, 1897 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1275 - 1298, 1897 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1299 - 1338, 1897 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1339 - 1354, 1898 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1355 - 1382, 1898 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1383 - 1406, 1898 - 1899 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1407 - 1430, 1899 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1431 - 1454, 1899 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1455 - 1478, c. 1899 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1479 - 1502, c. 1899 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1503 - 1526, c. 1899 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1527 - 1542, 1547 - 1550, c. 1899 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1551 - 1574, c. 1899 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1575 - 1598, c. 1899 (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1599 - 1622, c. 1899 (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1623 - 1646, c. 1899 (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1647 - 1670, c. 1899 (Box 36, Folder 48)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1671 - 1700, c. 1899 (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1705 - 1728, c. 1899 (Box 36, Folder 50)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1729 - 1752, c. 1899 (Box 36, Folder 51)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1753 - 1776, c. 1899 (Box 36, Folder 52)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1777 - 1788, 1793 - 1800, c. 1899 (Box 36, Folder 53)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1801 - 1824, c. 1899 (Box 36, Folder 54)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1825 - 1848 (Box 36, Folder 55)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1849 - 1872 (Box 36, Folder 56)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1873 - 1896 (Box 36, Folder 57)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1901 - 1918 (Box 36, Folder 58)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1919 -1942 (Box 36, Folder 59)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1943 - 1966 (Box 36, Folder 60)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1967 - 1990 (Box 36, Folder 61)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 1991 - 2014 (Box 36, Folder 62)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2015 - 2044 (Box 36, Folder 63)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2047 - 2076 (Box 36, Folder 64)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2077 - 2100, 1901 (Box 36, Folder 65)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2101 - 2104, 2109 - 2112, 2117 - 2124, c. 1901 (Box 36, Folder 66)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2125 - 2136, 2141 - 2148, c. 1901 (Box 36, Folder 67)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2149 - 2172 (Box 36, Folder 68)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2173 - 2196 (Box 36, Folder 69)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2197 - 2220 (Box 36, Folder 70)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2221 - 2244 (Box 36, Folder 71)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2245 - 2268, 1901 - 1902 (Box 36, Folder 72)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2269 - 2292, 1901 - 1902 (Box 36, Folder 73)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2293 - 2316, 1901 - 1902 (Box 36, Folder 74)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2317 - 2340, c. 1901 - 1902 (Box 36, Folder 75)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2341 - 2364, c. 1901 - 1902 (Box 36, Folder 76)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2365 - 2394, c. 1901 - 1902 (Box 36, Folder 77)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2395 - 2422, 1901 - 1902 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2427 - 2446, 1901 - 1902 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2447 - 2470, 1898 - 1902 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2471 - 2478, 2483 - 2494 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2495 - 2518 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2519 - 2530, 2535 - 2542 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2543 - 2566 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2567 - 2590 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2591 - 2614 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2615 - 2626, 2631- 2638, 1902 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2639 - 2662 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2664 - 2686 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2687- 2702, 2707 - 2710 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2711 - 2737 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2738 - 2781, 1902 - 1903 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2822 - 2857, 1902 - 1903 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2898 - 2937, 1902 - 1903 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2938 - 2949, 2954 - 2977, 1901 - 1903 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 2978 - 2997, 3002 - 3017, 1902 - 1904 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3018 - 1049, 1903 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3050 - 3073, 1904 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3074 - 3083, 1903 - 1904 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3084 - 3115, 3120 - 3127, 1903 - 1904 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3128 - 3135, 3140 - 3167, 1904 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3168 - 3203, 1904 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3204 - 3207, 3212 - 3243, 1904 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3244 - 3283, 1898 - 1904 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3284 - 3299, 3308 - 3323, 1904 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3324 - 3355, 1904 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3356 - 3387 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3388 - 3415, 1904 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3420 - 3463 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3464 - 3487, 3544 - 3555 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3560 - 3591 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3592 - 3631 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3632 - 3671, 1906 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3672 - 3711, 1905 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3712 - 3751 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3752 - 3783, 1905 - 1906 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3784 - 3791, 3796 - 3817 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3818 - 3938 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3939 - 3978, 1906 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 3979 - 3998, 4003 - 4014 (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4015 - 4054 (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4055 - 4094 (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4095 - 4174, 1906 (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4175 - 4206, 1906 (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4238 - 4281 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - 5 x 7, Prints (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4283 - 4321, 1906 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4322 - 4345 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4346 - 4365, 1906 - 1907 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4366 - 4385, 1906 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4386 - 4404, 1906 - 1907 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4405 - 4424, 1906 - 1907 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4425 - 4439, 1906 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4457 - 4472, 4477 - 4492 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4493 - 4524 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4525 - 4540, 4545 - 4556, 1908 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4557 - 4588, 1908 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 4589 - 5016, 1908 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 5017 - 5068, 1908 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - 5 x 7, Print Numbers: 5069 - 5086, 1908 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: one - 24, 1891 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 25 - 48, 1890 - 1891 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 49 - 72, 1890 - 1891 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 73 - 96, 1891 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 97 -104, 109 - 120, 1891 - 1892 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 121 - 144, 1891 - 1892 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 145 - 168, 1892 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 169 - 172, 177 - 188, 1891 - 1892 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 193 - 204, 209 - 216, 1892 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 217 - 236, 1892 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 241 - 264, 1892 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 265 - 288, 1891 - 1893 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 289 - 312, 1893 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 313 - 338, 1893 - 1895 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 339 - 362, 1894 - 1895 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 363 - 386, 1894 - 1895 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 387 - 410, 1894 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 411 - 430, 1894 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 431 - 434, 439 - 454, 1892 -1894 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 455 - 478, 1894 - 1895 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 479 - 502, 1895 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 503 - 526, 1895 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 527 - 550, 1894 - 1895 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 555 - 574, 1895 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 575 - 598, 1895 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 599 - 622, 1895 (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 623 - 650, 1895 - 1896 (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 651 - 670, 1896 (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 671 - 700, 1895 - 1896 (Box 38, Folder 45)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 701 - 724, 1896 (Box 38, Folder 46)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 725 - 748, 1896 (Box 38, Folder 47)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 749 - 772, 1896 (Box 38, Folder 48)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 773 - 796, 1896 (Box 38, Folder 49)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 797 - 800, 805 - 820, 1896 (Box 38, Folder 50)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 821 - 844, 1896 - 1897 (Box 38, Folder 51)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 845 - 860, 865 - 868, 1897 (Box 38, Folder 52)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 869 - 892, 1899 (Box 38, Folder 53)
    - 5 x 8, Print Numbers: 893 - 921 (Box 38, Folder 54)
    - 6.5 x 8.5, Print Numbers: one - 20, 1889 - 1890 (Box 38, Folder 55)
    - 6.5 x 8.5, Print Numbers: 21 - 48, 1890 - 1891 (Box 38, Folder 56)
    - 6.5 x 8.5, Print Numbers: 49 - 72, 1889 - 1890 (Box 38, Folder 57)
    - 6.5 x 8.5, Print Numbers: 73 - 96, 1889 - 1890 (Box 38, Folder 58)
    - 6.5 x 8.5, Print Numbers: 97 - 120, 1889 - 1890 (Box 38, Folder 59)
    - 6.5 x 8.5, Print Numbers: 145 - 168, 1891 - 1892 (Box 38, Folder 60)
    - 6.5 x 8.5, Print Numbers: 173 - 192, 1892 - 1893 (Box 38, Folder 61)
    - 6.5 x 8.5, Print Numbers: 193 - 216, 1893 - 1899 (Box 38, Folder 62)
    - 6.5 x 8.5, Print Numbers: 217 - 236 (Box 38, Folder 63)
    - 6.5 x 8.5, Print Numbers: 237 - 260 (Box 38, Folder 64)
    - 6.5 x 8.5, Print Numbers: 261 - 316, 1902 - 1904 (Box 38, Folder 65)
    - 6.5 x 8.5, Print Numbers: 317 - 323, 1892 (Box 38, Folder 66)
    - 8 x 10, Print Numbers: one - 12, 1889 - 1892 (Box 38, Folder 67)
    - 8 x 10, Print Numbers: 13 - 24, 1891 - 1893 (Box 38, Folder 68)
    - 8 x 10, Print Numbers: 25 - 36, 1893 - 1896 (Box 38, Folder 69)
    - 8 x 10, Print Numbers: 37 - 48 (Box 38, Folder 70)
    - 8 x 10, Print Numbers: 49 - 60 (Box 38, Folder 71)
    - 8 x 10, Print Numbers: 61 - 72 (Box 38, Folder 72)
    - 8 x 10, Print Numbers: 73 - 89 (Box 38, Folder 73)
    - 8 x 10, Print Numbers: 90 - 102, 1905 - 1906 (Box 38, Folder 74)
    - 8 x 10, Print Numbers: 107 - 113 (Box 38, Folder 75)
    - 8 x 10, Print Numbers: 114 - 119 (Box 38, Folder 76)
    - Cyanotypes removed from albums (Box 54)
    - Cyanotypes removed from albums (Box 55)
    - Cyanotypes removed from albums (Box 56)
    - Cyanotypes removed from albums (Box 57)
    - Cyanotypes removed from albums (Box 58)
    - Cyanotypes removed from albums (Box 59)
    - Cyanotypes removed from albums (Box 60)
    - Cyanotypes removed from albums (Box 61)
    - Cyanotypes removed from albums (Box 62)
    - Cyanotypes removed from albums (Box 63)
  - Cyanotype Negatives
    - Glass negatives (Box 49)
    - Glass negatives (Box 50)
    - Glass negatives (Box 51)
    - Glass negatives (Box 52)
    - Glass negatives (Box 53)
    - Glass negatives (Box 67)
    - Glass negatives (Box 68)
    - Glass negatives (Box 69)
    - Glass negatives (Box 70)
- Series XI. Honors and Awards, 1888-2004
  - Bailey memorabilia: dinner menus, essay, poetry 1888-1949 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bailey memorabilia: dinner souvenir box 1912, MU-1344
  - L.H. Bailey Monument 1913 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - L.H.B. 80th Birthday material 1938 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - James Knapp essay for 90th birthday; Essay in Land Policy Review 1941, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Honors 1941 - 1958 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Certificate from the American Horticultural Council, Citation for Outstanding Accomplishments presented Honoring Ethel Zoe Bailey. Also includes letter to Bailey from President of Council, Phillip Alampi, October 31, 1956. 1956 (Folder MSS Box 46)
  - Bailey Palm Glade information 1942 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Portrait material 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - L.H.B. 90th & 95th Birthday material 1942-1948, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Arthur Bartlett Correspondence and "How to Be Young at Ninety" 1946 - 1948 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - L.H.B. 90th Birthday material 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - L.H.B. 90th Birthday material 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - L.H.B. 90th Birthday material 1948 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - "Words Said About a Birthday" 1948 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - American Agricultural Editors' Association Award 1948 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - "Words Said About a Birthday" 1948 (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - Bailey Dinner Menu and Guest Lists 1948 (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - "Words Said About a Birthday" correspondence 1949 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - L.H.B. 90th Birthday material 1949 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Portrait Bust 1951 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Tributes 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 21)